[Shin Yoo-il scandal]
[Shin Yoo-il is
Dating a Guy?]
["Isn't that a Fake?"]
[Shin Yoo-il
the Shindecent!]
[Gender doesn't matter
but Honesty does!]
Have you been
waiting for me?
How could we not?
Our one and only actor
has a scandal with
a superstar Shin Yoo-il!
I'm not sure
I heard some bad rumors
about this guy
His nickname is
"Shindecent"
because he's
so indecent, right?
Still, he's the best
brand in showbiz
who's most wanted
by advertisers
Thanks to him
people are talking
about you, Hyesung!
She's right
You should be grateful
But ma'am…
[President Goo]
It's the president
of Shin Yoo-il's agency
Hello, sir
It's been a while
Are you serious now?
Okay, I got it
They wanna
make it official
What?
Have I kept you waiting?
Yes
for quite a long time
Sorry
I took the wrong train
How could you
not recognize me?
What about you?
Did you recognize me?
Sure, I did
You're Yoon Minhyung
in "My Crazy Family"
Right
I used to be well known
as that character
Let's date
What?